Guide to The Billie Jean King Collection 1901-2019 (bulk, 1940-2019) MS 3147
New-York Historical Society
- Series VII. Print matter, 1901-2020 (bulk, 1940-2020); 19 Linear feet in 14 record cartons, 4 flat boxes, and various oversize folders
  Series VII. Print matter contains printed material collected by BJK, including newspaper clippings, magazines and journals, event programs, books, ephemera, and posters. The clippings, magazines, and journals document BJK's career, as well as tennis and women's sports more generally. The programs files document BJK's activities as an attendee of sporting and fundraising events. Many of the books in the series were signed by the author and inscribed to BJK, and their topics reflect BJK's interest and work in business and LGBTQ and women's equality. Ephemera in the series contains various single items, such as autographs, event tickets, and magazine covers featuring BJK. Posters include tennis match posters, advertisements featuring BJK, and political posters and signs. Material dates from 1901 to 2019, with the bulk dates of 1940 to 2019.
  Arranged in six subseries:
  Subseries VII.A. Clippings
  Subseries VII.B. Magazines and journals
  Subseries VII.C. Programs
  Subseries VII.D. Books
  Subseries VII.E. Ephemera
  Subseries VII.F. Posters
  - Subseries VII.A. Clippings, 1943-2020; 2 Linear feet in 2 record cartons
    Subseries VII.A contains newspaper and magazine clippings from local, national, and international papers with articles spanning 1943-2019. Topics of articles include BJK's early tennis career, various tournaments, TeamTennis, World TeamTennis, the Battle of the Sexes match, Virginia Slims Circuit, and BJK's efforts toward gender equality, as well as various interviews. Publications include the Independent Press Telegram, Los Angeles Times, New York Times, San Francisco Chronicle, and USA Today.
    Files are arranged in chronological order. Articles clipped without visible publication dates are grouped together by decade, their assumed date determined by context and topical matter. Clipped articles that include dates are arranged in a folder for each year, with multiple folders when the amount of material dictates.
    Additional clippings in the collection are located in Series II scrapbooks.
    - 1940s (Offsite-box 28, Folder 6)
    - 1950s (Offsite-box 28, Folder 7)
      Topics include BJK's junior tennis career, play in under-15 tournaments, and coach Clyde Walker.
    - 1960s (3 folders) (Offsite-box 28, Folder 8-10)
      Topics include play at the Pacific Southwest Open, Wimbledon, rankings, and BJK's brother Randy Moffitt's baseball career.
    - 1960-1969 (21 folders) (Offsite-box 28, Folder 11-31)
      Clippings are organized into folders by year.
      Topics of articles include the Junior Wightman Cup, Wimbledon championships, various tournaments, world rankings, and wedding to Larry King. Publications include the Evening Standard, Independent Press Telegram of Long Beach, California, The Los Angeles Times, San Francisco Examiner, and World Tennis.
    - 1970s (4 folders) (Offsite-box 28, Folder 32-35)
      Topics include World TeamTennis, the Virginia Slims Circuit, and Randy Moffitt's baseball career. Publications include the New York Post, The New York Times, and The Independent Press Telegram.
    - 1970-1973 (13 folders) (Offsite-box 28, Folder 36-48)
      Topics of articles include the Wightman Cup, US Open championships, Wimbledon championships, USLTA, BJK Invitational tournament, the Virginia Slims Circuit, the 1973 "Battle of the Sexes" match with Bobby Riggs, and brother Randy Moffitt. Publications include the Dallas Morning News, Independent Press Telegram, Long Angeles Times, San Francisco Chronicle, San Francisco Examiner, and World Tennis Magazine.
    - 1974-1979 (8 folders) (Offsite-box 29, Folder 1-8)
      Topics include the Virginia Slims tournament, Wimbledon championships, World TeamTennis, and TeamTennis. Publications include the Dallas Morning News, Independent Press Telegram, the New York Post, The New York Times, Tennis Week, and Sports Illustrated.
    - 1980s (Offsite-box 29, Folder 9)
      Contains articles on Randy Moffitt's career as a Major League Baseball pitcher.
    - 1980-1989 (9 folders), 1981-1989 (Offsite-box 29, Folder 10-18)
      Topics include the Avon Championships, International Tennis Hall of Fame induction, TeamTennis league, and Wimbledon championships. Publications include the Independent Press Telegram, Los Angeles Herald Examiner, Pro Tennis Magazine, San Francisco Examiner, and USA Today.
    - 1990-1999 (11 folders) (Offsite-box 29, Folder 19-29)
      Topics include coaching, the International Women's Hall of Fame, TeamTennis, and the US Open. Publications include the Charlotte Observer, Chicago Sun-Times, Chicago Tribune, the National Sports Daily, and USA Today.
    - 2000s (3 folders) (Offsite-box 29, Folder 30-32)
      Topics include the Long Beach Century Club, World TeamTennis, and retrospectives of BJK's career and the Battle of the Sexes match. Publications include the Arizona Republic, Daily Courier, and the Press Telegram.
    - 2000-2009 (19 folders) (Offsite-box 29, Folder 33-51)
      Article topics include BJK's work in television commentary, Title IX, TeamTennis, World TeamTennis, the "When Billie Beat Bobby" film, the HBO documentary "Billie Jean King: Portrait of a Pioneer," and the naming of the USTA BJK National Tennis Center. Publications include the Desert Sun, the New York Times, San Diego Union-Tribune, USA Today, and the Wall Street Journal.
    - USTA BJK National Tennis Center naming (2 folders), 2006 August 29 (Offsite-box 40, Folder 6-7)
      Contains copies of the New York Times issue and sports section with story on the naming ceremony. Issues signed and dated by BJK.
    - 2010-2019 (13 folders) (Offsite-box 29, Folder 52-64)
      Topics include World TeamTennis, the "Battle of the Sexes" film, and the BBC's Sports Personality of the Year lifetime achievement award. Publications include the Desert Sun, New York Times, Washington Post, and USA Today.
    - 2018-2020 (Offsite-box 64, Folder 16)
  - Subseries VII.B. Magazines and journals, 1958-2018; 11.5 Linear feet in 5 record cartons and 4 flat boxes
    Subseries VII.B includes complete issues of magazines, periodicals, and journals. Publications may include articles on BJK, a BJK cover, or may contain general sports and tennis news. Publication entries include variable numbers of issues, and certain titles contain only one issue. Notable publications with multiple issues include TENNIS magazine and World Tennis. Publications date from 1958-2018.
    Arranged alphabetically by publication title.
    - A-B, 1967-2012 (Offsite-box 29, Folder 65)
      Contains the following issues: American Fitness July/August 1991; Association for Women in Sports Media Fall 2005; Athletic Business May 1988; Atlantic Racquet Press Fall 2005 and Winter 2005; Avon Calling 1977; Biography Magazine September 1998; Black Tennis Holiday Special 2012; Bride and Groom Fall-Winter 1967.
    - Billboard, 1975-2006 (Offsite-box 40, Folder 8)
      Contains Billboard issues dated April 12, 1975 and October 14, 2006.
    - C (2 folders), 1967-2010 (Offsite-box 30, Folder 1-2)
      Includes issues of California Tennis Vol. 1 No. 2-10 1967-1968; Chicago Tribune Magazine July 9, 2000; Circulation June 1971; Clipper Magazine June-July 1968; Continental August 2010; Cue June 4, 1976 and August 20, 1976; and Current Biography 1967 December.
    - E-H (4 folders), 1973-2016 (Offsite-box 30, Folder 3-6)
      Contains the following issues: Entertainment Weekly September 30, 2005; ESPN The Magazine June 11 2012; Esquire October 1974; Exchange Summer 2005; Family Circle May 1973; FIFA 1904 April 2016; Fitness October 2005; Fortune October 1, 2017; Glamour December 2006; GO NYC September 1-October 6, 2006 and June 8-August 3, 2007; Good Housekeeping March 1974; and Harrisburg Magazine October 2005.
    - ESPY, 1999 (Offsite-box 40, Folder 9)
      Contains ESPY Awards Special Collector's Issue: The Greatest Year Ever 1998.
    - I-L (5 folders), 1963-2012 (Offsite-box 30, Folder 7-11)
      Contains the following issues: Indianapolis Tennis Magazine Summer 2007 and Fall/Winter 2012; Inside Women's Tennis July 1987 and November 1990; International Women's Professional Softball [c. 1976]; Interview July 2006 with BJK preparatory notes for interview with Roger Federer; The Journal on Active Aging July/August 2006; Kristall-News life 2006; Ladies' Home Journal April 1974 and July 1974; Lambda Legal Updated Summer 2006; Long Beach Review June 1989; Long Island Tennis July 1975; and Los Angeles Magazine July 1963; Los Angeles Tennis Magazine January/February 1995.
    - The Illustrated London News, 1961 July 15 (Offsite-box 40, Folder 10)
    - Inside Tennis, 2005-2006 (Offsite-box 41, Folder 1)
      Contains October 2005 and September 2006 issues.
    - Legacies: The Historical Society of Pennsylvania, 2018 Fall (Offsite-box 67, Folder 9)
    - LIFE (4 folders), 1958-1976 (Offsite-box 41, Folder 2-5)
      Contains the following issues: 1939 August 28, 1968 September 20, 1971 November 19, 1973, Special Report: 1973 The Year in pictures, Special Report: Remarkable American Women 1776-1976.
    - M (4 folders), 1988-2017 (Offsite-box 30, Folder 12-15)
      Contains the following issues: Making Waves No. 2 and No. 3, 2007; Marie Claire September 2017; Matchpoint May 27-June 11 2004; Me September/October 2007; Melpomene Winter 2002; Men's Health October 2005; Merrill Lynch Advisor Spring-Summer 2006; Ms. July 1973, February 1988, and Fall 2007; National Gay and Lesbian Task Force publications from 1999 and 2000.
    - N (3 folders), 1991-2018 (Offsite-box 31, Folder 1-3)
      Contains the following issues: NetPLAY Winter 2013; New Jersey Goodlife June 1991; New Woman December l991; New York February 26, 2007; The New York Times Magazine August 26, 2012; August 27, 2017; November 12, 2017; The New York Times Sports Magazine, September 2007; New York Woman August 1998; The New Yorker February 3, 2003; Newsweek July 19, 1999, July 26, 1999, August 2, 1999, and She Persisted Special Edition 2018.
    - New York SmartCEO, 2014 July/August (Offsite-box 41, Folder 6)
    - The New York Times Magazine, 1967 August 27 (Offsite-box 42, Folder 1)
    - O-R (8 folders), 1971-2016 (Offsite-box 31, Folder 4-11)
      Contains the following issues: Occidental Spring 2016; OK! July 11, 2006; Orange Coast September 2006; Out & Equal Winter 2004; OUT August 2017; Overtime Magazine Spring/Summer 2006; People February 3, 1975, June 14, 1976, October 10, 1977, May 25, 1981, September 12, 1983, and September 12, 2005; Peristyle Winter 1978; Philanthropy World volume 12 issue 2, 2007; PhillySport August 1989; Playboy March 1975; Point of Contact March 1988; Real Simple February 2013; Real Sports Winter 1999 and Spring 2002; Redbook October 1971; Richmond Magazine December 2018; and Robin Hood The Heroes Edition 2011.
    - PACE, 1968 November (Offsite-box 42, Folder 2)
    - Paper magazine, 2018 Summer (Offsite-box 67, Folder 10)
    - Parade, 1967-1984 (Offsite-box 42, Folder 3)
      Contains the following issues: 1967 September 3, 1978 March 26, and 1984 January 8.
    - PCMA Daily, 2019 January 8 (Offsite-box 42, Folder 4)
    - S (4 folders), 1988-2016 (Offsite-box 31, Folder 12-15)
      Contains the following issues: The Saturday Evening Post March 1988; Smithsonian Spring 2015; Soul Sport December 2014, July 2016, and December 2016; Sports Illustrated for Kids June 2003 and July 2003; Sports inc. May 30, 1988; SportsPro Dec/Jan 2013, February 2013, March 2013, and September 2014; and Standford Center on Ethnics Title IX today, Title IX Tomorrow, 2007.
    - The Saturday Evening Post, 1975 March (Offsite-box 42, Folder 5)
    - Seventeen, 1975 January (Offsite-box 42, Folder 6)
    - Southland (3 folders), 1958-1968 (Offsite-box 32, Folder 1-3)
      Contains issues of Southland: Magazine of the Sunday Independent Press Telegram of Long Beach, California, BJK's hometown. Issues contain articles on BJK's early tennis career with Coach Clyde Walker, Juniors tennis career, and play at Wimbledon. BJK appears on cover of each issue. The issues date March 2, 1958; March 10, 1963; June 25, 1967; and September 8, 1968.
    - Sports Illustrated (4 folders), 1959-2012 (Offsite-box 32, Folder 4-7)
      Contains issues of Sports Illustrated dated February 16, 1959; July 9, 1962, July 15, 1963; July 17, 1967; September 18, 1967; June 24, 1968; July 17, 1892; December 25, 1972; July 16, 1973; May 19, 1975; April 4, 1983; June 20, 1983; April 29, 1991; May 16, 2005; December 6, 2010; and May 7, 2012.
    - Street & Smith's SportsBusiness JOURNAL (3 of 5 folders), 2005 April-2015 April (Offsite-box 42, Folder 7-9)
      Contains the following issues: 2005 April 25-May 1, June 20-26, June 27-July 3, July 11-17, July 25-31, August 1-7, September 12-18, September 19-25, September 26-October 2, October 3-6, October 10-16, October 17-23, October 24-30, October 31-November 6, and November 14-20.
    - Street & Smith's SportsBusiness JOURNAL (2 of 5 folders), 2005 April-2015 April (Offsite-box 43, Folder 1-2)
      Contains the following issues: 2005 November 21-27, 2008 July 7-13, 2011 October 10-16, October 8-14, 2013 September 9-15, and 2015 April 6-12 special advertising insert for Mylan World TeamTennis 40th season.
    - Super Tiebreaker (2 folders), 1976-1991 (Offsite-box 32, Folder 8-9)
      Contains issues of Super Tiebreaker, the offical magazine of World TeamTennis, Team Tennis, and Domino's Pizza TeamTennis. The title of the magazine is stylized on various issues as "Super-tiebreaker," "Super tie-breaker," and "Supertiebreaker." Content of each issue includes articles and interviews with coaches and players, team lineups, player bios, and rules of play. Issues date for the seasons of 1976, 1977, 1978, 1981, 1985, 1989, and 1991.
    - T (5 folders), 1967-2018 (Offsite-box 32, Folder 10-14)
      Contains the following issues: Tennis Illustrated 1967 and November 1974; Tennis Industry July 1989 and September/October 2014; Tennis View Magazine January/February 2013; Tennis Week May 7, 1998, June 27, 2002, September 1, 2002, October 24, 2002, October 25, 2005, December 2007, and July 2008; TennisPro March/April 2016; Tennis West/East November 1973; TIME September 15, 1967, January 5, 1976, October 20, 1997, December 26, 2005/January 2, 2006, October 9, 2017, and December 24/December 31, 2018; and The Times Magazine September 27, 2008.
    - TENNIS (3 of 5 folders), 1968-2017 (Offsite-box 32, Folder 15-17)
      Contains issues of TENNIS. Issues dated April 1968, July 1970, November 1987, October 1988, November 1988, April 1989, August 1998, July 2003, March 2004, July 2004, October 2006, November/December 2006, October 2007, November/December 2007, September 2008, July/August 2014, September/October 2014, and September/October 2017.
    - TENNIS (2 of 5 folders), 1968-2017 (Offsite-box 33, Folder 1-2)
      Contains issues of TENNIS. Issues dated October 2006, November/December 2006, October 2007, November/December 2007, September 2008, July/August 2014, September/October 2014, and September/October 2017.
    - Tennis U.S.A. (5 folders), 1964-1969 (Offsite-box 33, Folder 3-7)
      Contains issues of Tennis U.S.A. Issues are dated June 1964, January-November 1966, January-December 1967, January-December 1968, and January-July 1969.
    - Tennis-Revue, 1967 July (Offsite-box 43, Folder 3)
      German tennis magazine.
    - U-W (6 folders), 1962-2017 (Offsite-box 33, Folder 8-13)
      Contains the following issues: The Ultimate Sports Guide, 2007 Fall/Winter; USA Weekend April 4-6, 2008; USLTA Championships Magazine 1962, 1968, and 1973; USTA Magazine September/October 2008; Vanity Fair November 2017; Weekend Sports December 28, 1975; Westways June 1985; Woman's Day October 27, 1987; Women in Sport: The State of Play 2006; Women's International Tennis Association August 29, 1988; Women's Sports & Fitness September/October 1998; Working Woman September 1988; World TeamTennis 1974 and 1975 seasons; and WTA The Legend November 2013.
    - WEST Los Angeles Times Magazine, 1968-1972 (Offsite-box 43, Folder 4)
      Contains the 1968 September 1 and 1972 September 3 issues.
    - Women's Sports Foundation annual report [removed from frame], 1999, 2002 (Offsite-box 45, Folder 6)
    - womenSports (2 folders), 1974-1977 (Offsite-box 33, Folder 14-15)
      Contains issues of womenSports magazine. Issues are dated June 1974 (the inaugural issue with BJK cover and "How to Win" article); February 1975; May 1975; May 1976; and May 1977.
    - World Tennis (2 of 15 folders), 1964-1989 (Offsite-box 33, Folder 16-17)
      Contains issues of World Tennis. Issues date September 1964, August 1965, October-December 1965, and January-June 1966.
    - World Tennis (13 of 15 folders), 1964-1989 (Offsite-box 34, Folder 1-13)
      Contains issues of World Tennis dated 1966 July-December; 1967 January-December; 1968 January-December; 1969 January-August; 1970 November; 1971 April and July; 1973 January, June, and November-December; 1975 March; 1983 April; 1985 May; 1988 September; and 1989 August.
  - Subseries VII.C. Programs, 1941-2018; 1 Linear feet in 1 record carton
    Subseries VII.C includes programs for events attended by BJK. Most programs are from tennis matches and tournaments. Additional events include other sporting events and fundraising events. Programs date from 1941-2018.
    Additional event programs are located in Series V. Awards and recognition within files for individual awards.
    - 1940s-1950s (Offsite-box 35, Folder 1)
      Contains program for the Professional Tennis Tour 1941 season and for Jack Kramer presents World's Professional Championship Tennis opening match 1959.
    - 1960s (3 folders) (Offsite-box 35, Folder 2-4)
      Contains programs for the following events: Pacific Southwest Tennis Championships 1961; Wimbledon Lawn Tennis Championships 1964, 1967, and 1968; Wightman Cup Matches 1967; the 1967 Davis Cup; National Tennis League presents Professional Tennis 1968; Pacific Southwest Open Tennis Championships 1968; the 1969 L.A. Invitational; and the Boulder Collegians 1969 season.
    - 1970s (3 folders) (Offsite-box 35, Folder 5-7)
      Contains programs for the following events: BMC Women's Pro-Tennis Championships BJK Invitational 1971; the Phoenix Giants 1971 season; 1972 Virginia Slims Spring Circuit BMC Women's Pro-Tennis Championships; San Francisco Giants game 1972 June 11; Virginia Slims Circuit BMC Women's Pro-Tennis Championships 1973; Young Giants 1973 season; Tennis America tennis camps 1973; Young Giants 1974 season; Wimbledon Lawn Tennis Championships 1974, and 1975; Tennis Women WTA Fall 1976; and BJK Challenge Series 1978.
    - 1980s (2 folders) (Offsite-box 35, Folder 8-9)
      Contains programs from the following events: Avon Championships of Los Angeles 1981 and 1982; Wimbledon Lawn Tennis Championships 1984; Lincoln-Mercury Women's Tennis Classics 1984 and 1985; Family Circle Magazine Cup XIV 1986; and Long Beach Century Club Sports Night 1988.
    - 1990s (Offsite-box 35, Folder 10)
      Contains programs from the following events: Smith College Women's Basketball Centennial 1993; World TeamTennis All-Star Smas Hits 1994 August 24-25; California State University, Los Angeles 50, 1997; ESPY Awards 1999; and Women's Night '99.
    - Sports Illustrated's 20th Century Sports Awards, 1999 December 2 (Offsite-box 43, Folder 5)
    - 2000s-2010s (3 folders) (Offsite-box 35, Folder 11-13)
      Contains programs from the following events: BJK and friends Honoring Joe Shapiro 2003, 2006, and 2007; Wimbledon Lawn Tennis Championships 2005; and New England Patriots vs. Lions December 3, 2006; Elton John at Madison Square Garden 2007 March 25; 2008 So the World May Hear Awards Gala (program inscribed to BJK by Garth Brooks); presentation of the Presidential Medal of Freedom 2009 August 23; US Open 2010; USTA Icon Awards 2012; BNP Paribas WTA Finals Singapore 2014; 2016 Ellis Island Family Heritage Awards; and USTA BJK Girls' 16s and 18s National Championships 2018.
  - Subseries VII.D. Books, 1943-2019; 3.5 Linear feet in 4 record cartons
    Subseries VII.D includes books collected by BJK. Books may include an inscription to BJK from the author or an accompanying letter, which has been kept with the book if present. Topics of books include business, fitness, LGBTQ equality, sports, and women's equality. Notable books with inscriptions to BJK include Hillary Rodham and Chelsea Clinton's book, Gutsy Women. Additional notable books include the Virginia Slims Circuit media guide for the 1977 season and Benjamin Snyder's The History of World TeamTennis. Books date from 1943-2019.
    Arranged alphabetically by author.
    - Albright, Madeleine. Read My Pins: Stories from a Diplomat's Jewel Box, 2009 (Offsite-box 35, Folder 14)
      Signed by author.
    - Becker, Jo. Forcing the Spring: Inside the Fight for Marriage Equality, 2014 (Offsite-box 35, Folder 15)
    - Benko, Cathleen and Anne Weisberg. Mass Career Customization: Aligning the Workplace with Today's Nontraditional Workforce, 2007 (Offsite-box 35, Folder 16)
    - Berman, Ron. The Incredible Journey of the Wellington Tennis Twins, 2005 (Offsite-box 36, Folder 1)
    - Blaney, Dorothy Gulbenkian. A Woman's Perspective: Billie's Birthday Party, 2003 October (Offsite-box 36, Folder 2)
    - Bondar, Roberta. The Arid Edge of Earth, 2006 (Offsite-box 36, Folder 3)
      Inscribed to BJK by author.
    - Borland, Brian. Maynard 8 Miles, 2013 (Offsite-box 67, Folder 11)
    - Bourke, Dale Hanson. The Skeptic's Guide to the Global AIDS Crisis, 2004 (Offsite-box 36, Folder 4)
      Contains additional printed materials from Opportunity International.
    - Browne, John. The Glass Closet: Why Coming Out Is Good Business, 2014 (Offsite-box 36, Folder 5)
    - Bruno, Nancy. Beautiful Women: Celebrating Beauty in Stories and Stills, 2008 (Offsite-box 36, Folder 6)
      Includes inscription to BJK by author.
    - Bucklin, Linda Hale. Beyond His Control: Memories of a Disobedient Daughter, 2007 (Offsite-box 36, Folder 7)
      Contains inscription to BJK by author and inserted note.
    - Buren, Jodi. Superwomen, 2004 (Offsite-box 36, Folder 8)
      Foreword of book by BJK.
    - Citrin, James M. The Dynamic Path, 2007 (Offsite-box 67, Folder 12)
      Inscribed by author to BJK.
    - Clinton, Hillary Rodham. Women in Foreign Policy selected excerpts, 2012 March (Offsite-box 64, Folder 3)
    - Clinton, Hillary Rodham and Chelsea Clinton. Gutsy Women, 2019 (Offsite-box 36, Folder 9)
      Signed by authors and includes inserted note to BJK from HRC.
    - Conant, Douglas and Mette Norgaard. TouchPoints: Creating Powerful Leadership Connections in the Smallest of Moments, 2011 (Offsite-box 36, Folder 10)
    - Cooke, Nicole. The Breakaway, 2014 (Offsite-box 36, Folder 11)
      Includes inscription to BJK from author and inserted letter.
    - Cornwell, Patricia. Portrait of a Killer: Jack the Ripper Case Closed, 2002 (Offsite-box 64, Folder 1)
    - Covey, Stephen R. The 7 Habits of Highly Effective People, 1989 (Offsite-box 36, Folder 12)
      Includes inscription to BJK from Dave Fish and Dick Herbst.
    - Daugherty, Michael J. The Devil Inside the Beltway, 2013 (Offsite-box 36, Folder 13)
      Contains inscription to BJK from author.
    - Engebrecht, Pat. When Love is Not Enough, 2011 (Offsite-box 36, Folder 15)
    - de Angeli, Marguerite. The Door in the Wall, 1989 (Offsite-box 36, Folder 14)
    - Evansville Area Tennis Patrons. Serve it Up, 1982 (Offsite-box 37, Folder 1)